Guide to the Kensinger Jones Papers, 1934-2001 and undated RL.00648
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Advertising Agencies, 1952-1983 and undated
  - Campbell-Ewald Company, Detroit, 1957-1967 and undated
    - Clients
      - Florida Citrus Commission
        - Presentation, 1962 Sept. 14 (Box 17)
        - Presentation, 1963 Mar. 25 (Box 17)
        - Presentations, 1963: Jun. 22, Aug. 9, Sept. 4 (Box 17)
        - Presentation, 1964 Jul. 9 (Box 17)
        - Presentation, 1965 Sept. 1 (Box 17)
        - Presentation, 1965 Oct. 18-20 (Box 18)
        - Presentation, 1965 Dec. 8 (Box 18)
        - Publicity re termination of account, 1966 (Box 18)
        - Presentation, 1966 Mar. 2, 3 folders (Box 18)
      - Florists Telegraph Delivery Association
        - Presentation, 1962 Sept. 19 (Box 18)
        - Presentation, 1963 Apr. 18 (Box 18)
      - Folger Coffee Western Division; Presentation to Procter and Gamble, 1965 Sept. 2 (Box 19)
      - General Motors Corporation
        - Corporate advertising correspondence, memos, and scripts, 1962-1963 (Box 19)
        - Corporate advertising memos and correspondence, 1965 Jan. - Sept. (Box 19)
        - Corporate image: Memos; correspondence re television advertising for GM as an institution March - Sept., 1959 (Box 19)
        - Corporate image: Proposal by NBC to CECO for GM sponsorship of television program specials, 1959 (Box 19)
        - Sales Manager Presentation Jun. 3; General Motors Overseas Operations conference, Detroit, 1966 (Box 19)
        - Sale Managers Presentation Sept. 22; Opel Dealers, New York, 1966 (Box 19)
        - Working Agreement for advertising services with Euclid Division, 1966 (Box 19)
      - General Motors Institutional
        - Advertising proposals for "Informational Campaign" 1960-1961 (Box 19)
        - Corporate Image: articles and pamphlets, 1958-1959 (Box 19)
        - Corporate Image: correspondence and memoranda, 1958-1960 (Box 19)
        - Danny Kaye TV Special, October 30, 1960, sponsored by GM, 1960-1961, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Exploratory: correspondence and memos re institutional advertising, 1958-1960 (Box 20)
        - General Motors corporate Promotion Philosophy and Television Recommendations, 1959 (Box 20)
        - GM Spectacular television special featuring musicals by Lerner and Lowe; memos; correspondence, 1959 (Box 20)
        - GM Styling Center Project: Production of color slide film for speech by W.L. Mitchell at GM Conference at Greenbrier, W. Va.; correspondence, 1959 (Box 20)
        - Miscellaneous, including letter describing The General Motors Communications Program, 1962 (Box 20)
        - Motorama: articles, 1957-1958 (Box 20)
        - Motorama: correspondence and scripts for advertising film and stage shows, 1958-1959 (Box 20)
        - Television Programming, 1965 (Box 20)
        - Television Special: An Evening of Excellence memo and proposal, 1967 (Box 20)
        - TV Commercial Recall Study, 1960 (Box 20)
        - TV Presentation, 1959-1960 (Box 20)
        - TV Programming: scripts; memos; correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 21)
        - Used car campaign on theme of "reliability" and speech on reliability by S. E. Skinner, GM, 1960-1961 and undated (Box 21)
        - World's Fair Project - correspondence; memos about the GM exhibit at the 1964 World's Fair in New York, 1961 (Box 21)
      - Marathon Oil Company: Guarantee speech for presentation, 1964 Dec. 2; speeches, creative drafts, and research reports, 1963-1964 (Box 21)
      - Meadow Gold: presentation to Beatrice Foods, 1964 Apr. 8 and May 14 (Box 21)
      - Print Advertising Association: Board of Directors Meeting, Chicago, 1967 (Box 21)
      - Print Advertising Association: correspondence and memos, 1963-1964 (Box 21)
      - Print Advertising Association: correspondence and report of meeting with leaders of the Print Advertising Association, Chicago, 1967 Sept. 15 (Box 21)
      - Rockwell-Standard Corp.: Book re Colonel Rockwell 1963-1964, 4 folders (Box 21)
    - Corporate Advertising Booklets by Newsweek; correspondence re corporate image, [ca. 1959] (Box 22)
    - Creative Departments
      - Address announcing resignation from Campbell-Ewald Co., 1967 Nov. 27 (Box 22)
      - Ads to keep, 1960-1966, 3 folders (Box 22)
      - Awards, 1959, 1961-1966 (Box 22)
      - Booklet: I Wish Somebody Had Told Me That The Day I Started, ca. June, 1965 (Box 22)
      - College Recruitment Presentation for Northwestern University, 1965 (Box 22)
      - Communications Conferences
        - Don't Scramble Eggheads: correspondence, speech, and flip chart, 1964 Jul. 30 (Box 22)
        - Memorandum, 1967 (Box 22)
        - Memos, script, and drafts of March 5 conference, including the printed booklet, The Most Important intersection in American Business, 1965 (Box 22)
        - Notes and scripts of Feb. 8 conference; summary of March 20 conference, 1962 (Box 23)
        - Notes and script of Oct. 8 conference re A Comparative Look at DDB, Ogilvy, and CE [Campbell-Ewald] advertising, 1963 (Box 23)
      - Conferences: Another Important Intersection at Campbell-Ewald, based on the AAAA Connection at the Greenbrier, 1965 (Box 23)
      - Conferences: Summaries, 1963-1964 (Box 23)
      - Coordination with Account Management, 1963 (Box 23)
      - Coordination with Account Management, 1964 (Box 23)
      - Coordination with Account Group, esp. for the Burroughs Corp. and National Bank of Detroit ads, correspondence and memos, 1965 (Box 23)
      - Copy and Art Talk brochure, 1958-1965 (Box 23)
      - Creative Fellowships, 1967 (Box 23)
      - Creative Philosophy - The Four I's Booklet, summarizing the Campbell-Ewald Co. approach for new business prospects, 1963 (Box 23)
      - Creative-Research Clambake I, [n.d] (Box 23)
      - Creative Seminar (Campbell-Ewald Co.) - Program draft and scripts of sessions; memos and correspondence, including detailed evaluations, 1966 Dec. 1-2 (Box 23)
      - Films
        - An American in Paris: Introduction to storyboard for Chevrolet [1959 model] and copy of Cannes certificate for First Prize in Live Action Category, 1959 (Box 23)
        - Expo 1967, 1967 (Box 23)
        - The Horse and The Fiddle or the Creativity Film: background information, correspondence, drafts, and notes on use of film, 1958-1969, Folders 1-3 of 7 (Box 23)
        - The Horse and The Fiddle or the Creativity Film: background information, correspondence, drafts, and notes on use of film, 1958-1969, Folders 4-7 of 7 (Box 24)
        - The Importance of Being Interesting, 1963-1967, 3 folders (Box 24)
        - Magic Ride, 1960-1961 (Box 24)
      - Merchandizing correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 24)
      - Reorganization including appointment of Jones as creative Director and Executive Vice President, 1960-1961 and undated (Box 24)
      - Reorganization, 1961, 1964-1966 and undated (Box 24)
      - Reorganization - Final memos and charts 1966 Jan.-Apr. (Box 24)
      - Report to Stockholders re goals and accomplishments of the Creative Department, 1966 Nov. 8 (Box 24)
      - Salary Information including some organizational charts, 1964-1967 (Box 25)
      - Seminars, Workshops, Conferences: reports from various meetings, 1961-1966 (Box 25)
      - Staff and Department Heads memos, 1967 (Box 25)
      - A Study of the Campbell-Ewald Creative Department, June 26, 1967, 1967, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Summary of "Fourth Communications Conference of the Art Directors Club of New York, Symbology, 1959, Apr. 1-2 (Box 25)
      - Vice Presidency Recommendations, 1960-1967 (Box 25)
      - Videotape Reports, memos, correspondence re using videotape for television commercials, 1958-1959 (Box 25)
    - Detroit Riots - Memos by Jones re role of Campbell-Ewald Co. after riots Jun. 27-30, memos by Fenton Ludtke, re: public relations for the New Detroit Committee, 1967 (Box 25)
    - Ideas: memos on advertising for Chevrolet; Federal Department stores; and use of nature and landscape in place of billboards, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Management
      - By-Laws of Campbell-Ewald Co., as of Nov. 3; and resolution of appreciation of H. G. Little, 1966 (Box 26)
      - Campbell-Ewald Creed, 1961 (Box 26)
      - Campbell-Ewald Stock Ownership Policies, 1963-1967 (Box 26)
      - Creative Philosophy - Memos among the Executive Committee re changes to policies for the Creative Department, esp., in response to recent resignations, 1966 (Box 26)
      - Executive Committee Minutes, 1966 Jan. - Dec. (Box 26)
      - Executive Committee Minutes, 1967 (Box 26)
      - Executive Reorganization - Reports and Memos, 1964-1966 (Box 26)
      - Management Correspondence, 1967 (Box 26)
      - Management Review Subcommittee Reports and memos June, 1967 (Box 26)
      - Memos and correspondence between Jones and Campbell-Ewald Co. executives, 1961-1966 (Box 26)
      - Operating Committee, Confidence Bulletin Digest, nos. 1-3, Nov. 64 - May 65, 1964-1965 (Box 27)
      - Personnel structure of Campbell-Ewald Co. and divisions, 1967 (Box 27)
      - Policy-Finance Committee minutes, 1966 Jan. - May (Box 27)
      - Press release re appointment of Tom Adams as President of Campbell-Ewald, Feb. 11, 1958 (Box 27)
      - Reorganization of Campbell-Ewald Co. vis-a-vis the retirement of Lawrence R. Nelson, 1967 (Box 27)
      - Reorganization including 1961 Jun. 20 memo summarizing Jones's first years as Creative Director, 1960-1964 (Box 27)
      - Report by Arthur Kirn, consultant re executive reorganization and personnel management, [Sept. 25, 1967] and earlier articles, 1959, 1964, 1967 (Box 27)
      - Reports on Agency Compensation by E. A. Shirmer, 1965 (Box 27)
      - Statement of Policy for the Campbell-Ewald Company, 1960 (Box 27)
    - Michigan State University - Presentation to Journalism students, East Lansing, 1963, Feb. 27-28 (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Biographies of writers and clients' executive officers, 1966-1969 (Box 27)
      - Birthday tribute with artwork imitating Time magazine, 1963 (Box 27)
      - Federal Trade Commission: Jones's presentation on automotive commercials on television, 1965 Aug. (Box 27)
    - New Business (Box 28)
      - Admiral Corporation Presentation, 1966 Dec. 15 (Box 28)
      - Business Development Planning memos, 1960-1961 (Box 28)
      - Business Development Planning Report and exhibits for Analysis of New Business Planning, 1962, Apr. 24 (Box 28)
      - Business Development Planning, 1963-1964 (Box 28)
      - Hiram Walker, 1965 (Box 28)
      - Miscellaneous Contracts, 1964-1965 (Box 28)
      - Miscellaneous Contracts, 1966 (Box 28)
      - Miscellaneous Contracts, 1966-1967 (Box 28)
      - Miscellaneous Contracts, 1968-1970 (Box 28)
      - Montgomery Ward and Co., 1965 (Box 28)
      - New Business Policy - esp. at Campbell-Ewald Co. divisional offices in Chicago, New York, etc., memos, 1961-1967 (Box 28)
      - New Business Development, 1965 (Box 28)
      - Pipe of the Month Club, 1964 (Box 28)
    - Personal
      - Appointments to Creative Director postions at Campbell-Ewald Co., 1957, 1960 (Box 28)
      - Appointment to Executive Vice-President and Creative Director for Chevrolet, 1966 (Box 29)
      - Little Wonder Presentation for Bud Schirmer Retirement Party, 1966, Mar. 24 (Box 29)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 29)
      - Photographs of Campbell-Ewald Co. individuals, who worked on commercial receiving award for Best Commercial, American Film Festival at the Adcraft Club of Detroit, 1960, Oct. 21 (Box 29)
      - Resignation of Jones from Campbell-Ewald Co.: addresses, clippings, and correspondence, 1967 Nov. - Dec., 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Willard Hanes Retirement Party Los Angeles, California, 1966, Jan. 25-28 (Box 29)
  - D.P. Brother and Company, Detroit, 1968-1972 and undated
    Arranged alphabetically by subject, the series documents Jones's work as Creative Director and Executive Vice President of the agency and his work on the Oldsmobile account. DPB became a subsidiary of Leo Burnett Company, Chicago, in 1967 and was renamed Leo Burnett Company of Michigan in 1971. In January, 1971, Jones moved to Leo Burnett Company headquarters in Chicago, continuing to direct the creative activity for all Oldsmobile advertising. See also Leo Burnett Company subseries, 1971-1972, for material related to Oldsmobile advertising and to interoffice coordination between Chicago and Detroit.
    - AAAA [American Association of Advertising Agencies] Annual Meeting - Memo summarizing some sessions; letter Leo Burnett to Jones, 1968 May 9 (Box 29)
    - Appointment to D. P. Brother and Co. Senior V.P. and Creative Director Correspondence and news clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 29)
    - Appointment to Board of Directors - Correspondence, press release, news clippings, 1969 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence - change of address re Jones move from Detroit to Chicago, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Credentials Booklet - describing agency after merger with Leo Burnett Company, 1967 (Box 29)
    - Creative Department - Articles, 1968-1969 (Box 29)
    - How to be Creative in Chicago - Booklet with farewell comments when Jones moved from Detroit to Chicago, 1970, Dec. (Box 30)
    - Leo Burnett Company
      - Creative Presentation to Leo Burnett Company re Oldsmobile advertising, including Status report - non Oldsmobile Accounts, 1969 (Box 30)
      - Memoranda and correspondence re speech by Leo Burnett, Believability in Advertising and the Inherent Drama of the Product: includes magazine advertisements, 1969, Sept. 8 (Box 30)
      - Office memoranda and correspondence from Leo Burnett and officials in Chicago, 1962, 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 30)
      - Personal correspondence with colleagues at Burnett, 1966-1970 (Box 30)
      - Report to Leo Burnett Board of Directors about D. P. Brother Co. Detroit for Jan. - Sept., 1968 (Box 30)
      - Talk to Burnett staff upon joining D. P. Brother, 1968, Jan. 5 (Box 30)
      - Year-End Luncheon, 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - General Motors
      - Air Pollution Story - 1968report and newspaper articles, for public relations focus, 1968-1970 (Box 30)
      - Corporate Ideas - correspondence and memoranda, 1970 (Box 30)
      - General Motors Corporate Project, 1970-1971 (Box 30)
      - Institutional: Ideas from Previous Years, 1970, 1967-1968 (Box 30)
    - H. Salt, Esq. TV and Radio Presentation material including TV script for Man with a Mission 1969 (Box 30)
    - Oldsmobile (Box 31)
      - Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 31)
      - 1969 Model Year - Brochure (with Ken Jones creative input), 1968-1969 (Box 31)
      - 1970 Model Year
        - Marketing Plan Book, 1968-1969 Apr. 1: 1972, 1991, 2 folders (Box 31)
        - Print Materials: Engineering Report, Advance Ordering Information and Rally 350 - Olds Dealers' Winter Quarter Impact Program - Part Two, 1969-1970 (Box 31)
      - 1971 Model Year
        - Announcement; presentation, creative exhibits, 1970 Apr. 10 (Box 31)
        - Copy, 1970 (Box 31)
        - Correspondence, memoranda, reports, 1969-1970, Folders 1-2 of 3 (Box 31)
        - Correspondence, memoranda, reports, 1969-1970, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 32)
        - Marketing Plan Book, 1970 Apr. 10, 2 folders (Box 32)
        - Product Information, 1970 (Box 32)
      - Re: moving Olds account from Detroit to Chicago; copies of Detroit material given to Joe Greeley, 1970-1971 (Box 32)
      - Move Detroit to Chicago: Past-Present-Future: personnel and procedures for the Oldsmobile account, 1971-1972 (Box 32)
  - Wilding Company, Southfield, Mich., 1977-1982
    Arranged alphabetically by subject, this subseries documents Jones's part-time consulting work and includes correspondence, memos, brochures, and scripts for several projects. Of particular note are the Ford Marketing Institute seminars on advertising and marketing presented to car dealers, often at the annual National Automotive Dealers Association meetings. Included are the transcripts of interviews with several successful car dealers, which were used in the 1980 seminars. See also the Audiovisual Materials Series for film versions of the seminars.
    - Bernard, Wells, and Loving, Detroit, accounting firm, 1979, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Community National Bank, Pontiac, Mich., 1978-1979, 4 folders (Box 33)
    - Ford Marketing Institute
      - Correspondence from Ford dealers, re advertising seminar, 1978, Mar. (Box 33)
      - Retail Advertising/Promotion Seminar. Instructor's Script, 1978, Jun., 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Retail Advertising/Promotion Seminar: Interviews with Auto Dealers, 1979 (Box 33)
      - Retail Advertising/Promotion Seminar Presentation. Script, Dec. 1979, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Herrud's Thorn Apple Valley Meats. Advertising and Promotion Plan and correspondence, 1978 (Box 34)
    - Metropolitan Detroit Chevrolet Dealers. Presentation script for new business, 1977 Jun. (Box 34)
    - Michigan's Upper Peninsula - Official Travel Guide, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 34)
    - NADA National Convention. Script for Seminar, Mirror, Mirror on the Wall, 1980 Feb. (Box 34)
    - New Business
      - A Creative Approach to our Creative Client/Prospect Presentation, 1978-1979 (Box 34)
      - Notes and ads. On Advertising Oneself and State of the Art, undated (Box 34)
      - Presentation script. [Refers to six characteristics of a good advertising agency based on a speech by Chinese businessman, Jack Chau] [ca. 1977] (Box 34)
      - Presentation script, Wilding Dimension, 1978-1979 (Box 34)
      - Presentation script, Wilding Resultful Campaigns, [1978-1979] (Box 34)
    - Republic Automotive Parts. Scripts for creative presentations, 1978-1982 (Box 34)
    - Tennent, Richard: agreement and report, 1978 (Box 34)
    - Working Agreements, Client/Agency, 1978 (Box 34)
  - William R. Biggs/Gilmore, Kalamazoo, Mich., 1980-1983
    Arranged alphabetically by subject, this subseries includes agency newsletters, memoranda and correspondence related to Jones's evaluation of the creative activities of the newly merged company and print ads for various clients. As Creative Director, Jones worked part time through 1982 and as a consultant thereafter.
    - Communications Accountability, marketing brochure, 1985-1986 (Box 35)
    - Creative Supervisor Postion: memos, correspondence, and notes 1982-1983 (Box 35)
    - Gibson Appliance Company, 1982, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Kellogg Company. 1982 (Box 35)
    - Marketing Mirror," agency newsletter, 1982-1987 (Box 35)
    - New Business Presentation, 1982 Nov. (Box 35)
    - Reflections: From the Beaten Path, booklet by Peter Horst, re five years as Creative Director (Box 35)
    - Remarks Presented by Kensinger Jones, Agency Meeting, 1982 Jun. 14 (Box 35)
    - Traffic System and Purchasing Procedure, 1981 (Box 35)
    - Various advertisements for different clients, ca. 1980-1983 (Box 35)
    - Various clients. Memos, ca. 1980-1983 (Box 35)
- Correspondence and Memoranda, 1964-1974
  Arranged chronologically, this series consists of carbons of outgoing business and personal correspondence, and office memoranda related to the advertising campaigns of the several agencies. Additional correspondence, from 1964 to 1974, occurs in the Advertising Agencies Series. From 1982 to 1995, professional correspondence and memoranda are located in the Michigan State University Series. Miscellaneous personal correspondence appears in the Personal Series.
  - Campbell-Ewald Company, 1964 Jan. - 1965 Aug., 5 folders (Box 36)
  - Campbell-Ewald Company, 1965 Sept.- 1967 Jul., 7 folders (Box 37)
  - Campbell-Ewald Company, 1967 Aug.- 1967 Dec., 1 folder (Box 38)
  - D.P. Brother and Company, 1968 Jan. - 1969 Jul., 3 folders (Box 38)
  - D.P. Brother and Company, 1969 Aug. - 1970 Dec., 3 folders (Box 39)
  - Leo Burnett Company, 1971 Jan. - 1971 Dec., 3 folders (Box 39)
  - Leo Burnett Company, 1972 Jan. - 1972 Dec., 6 folders (Box 40)
  - Leo Burnett Company, 1973 Jan. - 1973 Mar., 1 folder (Box 41)
  - Leo Burnett Company Pty. Limited, Sydney, 1973 Apr. - 1974 Apr., 3 folders (Box 41)
  - Leo Burnett Pte. Limited, Singapore, 1974 May - 1974 Aug., 1 folder (Box 41)
- Michigan State University, 1982-1997 and undated
  Divided into two subseries, Subject Files and Course Materials, this series pertains to Jones's teaching activities, while he was a Lecturer in the Department of Advertising, in the School of Communication Arts, at Michigan State University in East Lansing, Mich.. (Material describing the curriculum or memos about Mr. Jones's teaching schedule are part of the Subject Files Subseries.)
  - Subject Files, 1982-1997 and undated
    Arranged alphabetically, the Subject Files Subseries consists of correspondence, primarily with students, conference papers, articles, newsletters, and departmental memoranda. Of particular note are the materials related to China. In 1988, Jones and his wife traveled throughout China with a U.S. Exchange program related to the advertising profession. In 1989, Jones conducted a weeklong seminar for advertising professionals in Taiwan and a similar seminar in East Lansing for visitors from Taiwan.
    - AAF (American Advertising Federation) National Student Advertising Competition, 1985 (Box 42)
    - Adcraft Foundation Scholarship Grants, 1991 (Box 42)
    - AEJMC (Association for Education in Journalism and Mass Communication) Conference, 1987, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - AEJMC-Correspondence re conference papers, 1987-1989 (Box 42)
    - Alumni Service Award-Nomination of Donald Keaton, Archway Cookies, Inc., 1987 (Box 42)
    - Archway Cookies, 1986-1989, 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Articles about advertising, 1960-1987 (Box 42)
    - Articles about advertising, 1992-1994 (Box 42)
    - ATandT seminar, 1985 Oct. 5 (Box 42)
    - Backley, Vincent J. Jr.- Silver Medalist speech, Ad Club of Cincinnati, 1986 (Box 42)
    - Cable Advertising: New Ways to New Business by M. Block, T. Baldwin and K. Jones, 1986 (Box 42)
    - China: Correspondence, 1988, 1990 (Box 42)
    - China: Proposal for exchange with Peoples University of China, 1989 (Box 42)
    - College of Arts and Sciences, Celebrity Lecture Series, 1993-1994 (Box 42)
    - College of Arts and Sciences, Dean's Community Council, 1993 (Box 42)
    - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1983-1988 and undated (Box 42)
    - The Creative Curriculum, Memo re creative advertising courses, 1985 Aug. 21 (Box 42)
    - Creative Strategy and Execution-Adv 317, Coordination proposal, 1985-1986 (Box 42)
    - Creativity: correspondence and articles, 1966-1992 and undated (Box 42)
    - Department of Advertising (Box 43)
      - Annual review of professional activities, 1985-1987 (Box 43)
      - Another Kind of Partnership, [undated] (Box 43)
      - Appointment and Reappointment Forms, 1983, 1989-1995 (Box 43)
      - Bachelor of Arts in Advertising, 1985 Feb. 1 (Box 43)
      - Course outlines of other courses, 1976-1987 and undated (Box 43)
      - Jim Gilmore and faculty position correspondence, 1987 Apr. (Box 43)
      - Job Correspondence, Jan-May 1989 (Box 43)
      - Memos, minutes, miscellaneous notes, 1983-1988, 1991-1993, 1996-1997 and undated (Box 43)
      - Request for a new course, 1985 (Box 43)
      - Salary negotiations, 1992, 1995 and undated (Box 43)
      - Teaching proposals, 1982, 1986 (Box 43)
      - United Way campaign, 1987 (Box 43)
    - Development Fund (College of Communication Arts and Sciences), 1987 (Box 43)
    - Guest lectures on writing and advertising, 1988-1989, 1992-1994 (Box 43)
    - Impact: Articles and correspondence for 1994 issue, 1993-1995 (Box 43)
    - Impact: Correspondence, speech, and print material, 1990-1995 (Box 43)
    - Impact: Draft of article about Jones in The Fifties by D. Halberstam, 1993 (Box 43)
    - Impact: Issues, 1991-1994 (Box 43)
    - Kellogg's Mueslix commercial, re permission to use, 1988 (Box 43)